<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2020 @ Duke on DataFest</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2020 @ Duke on DataFest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/coc.html</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at Duke is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq.html</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? You can click here to sign up. Registration will begin in February.
Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee. However note that the event takes significant resources to run. So, if you sign up, we expect that you will show up! If your plans change, let us know as soon as possible so we can make your spot available to someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>/media.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media.html</guid>
      <description>If you would like to write about or cover ASA DataFestTM in any way, please don&#39;t hesitate to contact us.
 DataFest Shows Spike in Growth, Provides Immersive Experience - AMSTAT News, September 1, 2017
 Edmunds.com sponsors data set for fifth ASA DataFest at UCLA - Daily Bruin - April 27, 2015
 DataFest draws hundreds to solve stats challenges - The Chronicle - March 23, 2015
 A Festival of Data: Student Perspectives - AMSTAT News, September 1, 2014</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule.html</guid>
      <description>DataFest will begin on Friday, April 3 at 6pm and end on Sunday, April 5 at 5pm.
Check back soon for a full schedule!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup.html</guid>
      <description>Click on the option that applies to you. Regardless of the option you choose, you will automatically be placed on the ASA DataFestTM mailing list to receive updates and announcements.
Registration deadline is March 18, 2020 at 11:59p.
Seats are limited, sign up before it&#39;s too late!
 If you are interested in serving as a consultant during the event, please let us know your availability [here](https://goo.gl/forms/nTUIDUpb8OiXy7j63). Alternatively, even if you&#39;re not competing, you&#39;re welcomed to attend the final presentations at 3pm on Sunday, April 8, at Penn Pavilion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors.html</guid>
      <description>A huge thanks to our 2020 sponsors! ASA DataFestTM at Duke cannot run without your support!
Click here for more information about how you can support DataFest at Duke. You can also contact us if you have any questions.

Cauchy Sponsors The Department of Statistical Science at Duke is nationally ranked in the top 5 research departments and as a top 10 graduate program. The Department currently (mid-late 2015) has 18 faculty, ~45 PhD students, ~70 MS students, ~70 research-active undergraduate majors, numerous postdocs, visitors, and affiliated researchers listed under People.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>/sponsorship.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsorship.html</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at Duke cannot run without your support!
Please see below for Sponsorship opportunities. Note that your donations are tax-deductible.
Please contact us if you are interested in sponsorship and/or have any questions.
Impact of Your Sponsorship Your sponsorship of ASA DataFestTM benefits the ASA DataFestTM @ Duke. Any residual funds will support undergraduate statistics education, foster the new generation of data science, and advance our mission of promoting the use of data in the understanding of our environment, our social relationships, and our physical and virtual selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops.html</guid>
      <description>The following workshops will be held at Duke, participants from all schools are welcome. See here for visitor parking information.
Dinner will be served at all workshops.
 Introduction to R: Data Transformations, Data Structures, and the Tidyverse by John Little
          &amp;nbsp; Sign up    &amp;nbsp; 03/17/2020    &amp;nbsp; 5:45pm - 8pm    &amp;nbsp; Bostock 127 (The Edge Workshop Room)    An introduction to R and the Tidyverse, using RStudio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>