<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataFest 2022 @ Duke on DataFest</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataFest 2022 @ Duke on DataFest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/coc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/coc.html</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at Duke is committed to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any event venue, including talks, workshops, social activities, social media, and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq.html</guid>
      <description>How do I sign up? Registration details will be announced in late February.

Is there a registration fee? No, there is no registration fee. However note that the event takes significant resources to run. So, if you sign up, we expect that you will show up! If your plans change, let us know as soon as possible so we can make your spot available to someone else.

Who is eligible to compete?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>/media.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media.html</guid>
      <description>If you would like to write about or cover ASA DataFestTM in any way, please don&#39;t hesitate to contact us.
 Winners Announced for Duke ASA DataFest COVID-19 Virtual Data Challenge - Duke Forge blog, May 8, 2020
 DataFest Shows Spike in Growth, Provides Immersive Experience - AMSTAT News, September 1, 2017
 Edmunds.com sponsors data set for fifth ASA DataFest at UCLA - Daily Bruin - April 27, 2015</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous DataFest Winners</title>
      <link>/winners.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/winners.html</guid>
      <description>emoji_events 2021 Winners

emoji_events 2020 Winners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources.html</guid>
      <description>Code repository, version control, and collaboration  GitLab: https://gitlab.oit.duke.edu/
 GitHub: https://www.github.com
 Happy Git with R: https://happygitwithr.com/
  Interactive dashboard:  Shiny
 Deploy Shiny app on shinyapps.io: https://docs.rstudio.com/shinyapps.io/getting-started.html Shiny tutorials: https://shiny.rstudio.com/tutorial/ Statistical Computing RShiny Notes: Part I and Part II   Tableau:
 Tableau Public: https://public.tableau.com/en-us/s Tableau Desktop - free student license: https://www.tableau.com/academic   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule.html</guid>
      <description>All event will take place in Penn Pavilion.
Friday, April 1, 2022 Welcome!
🔹 6pm: Kickoff &amp;amp; Meet the data
Consultants available for help 7p - midnight.
Saturday, April 2, 2022 Carry on!
🔹 9am: Breakfast
🔹 12pm: Lunch &amp;amp; Team activity
🔹 6pm: Dinner
Consultants available for help throughout the day.
Sunday, April 3, 2022 Wrap up!
🔹 9am: Breakfast
🔹 12pm: Lunch &amp;amp; projects due!
🔹 1pm: Round 1 judging</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up</title>
      <link>/signup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/signup.html</guid>
      <description>Click on the option that applies to you. Regardless of the option you choose, you will automatically be placed on the ASA DataFestTM mailing list to receive updates and announcements.
The registration deadline is March 25, 2022. Seats are limited, so sign up before it&#39;s too late!
Participants Option 1: Team sign-up (2-5 students)  Click here to sign up as a team of 2 to 5 students.

Option 2: Looking for teammates  If you do not have a team in mind but you&#39;re looking for teammates, click here to leave us your information so that you can be matched with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors.html</guid>
      <description>A huge thanks to our 2020 - 2021 sponsors! ASA DataFestTM at Duke cannot run without your support!
Click here for more information about how you can support DataFest at Duke. You can also contact us if you have any questions.

Cauchy Sponsors 
The Duke AI Health Institute connects, strengthens, amplifies, and grows multiple streams of theoretical and applied research on artificial intelligence in order to answer the most urgent and difficult challenges in medicine and population health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>/sponsorship.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsorship.html</guid>
      <description>ASA DataFestTM at Duke cannot run without your support!
Please see below for Sponsorship opportunities. Note that your donations are tax-deductible.
Please contact us if you are interested in sponsorship and/or have any questions.
Impact of Your Sponsorship Your sponsorship of ASA DataFestTM benefits the ASA DataFestTM @ Duke. Any residual funds will support undergraduate statistics education, foster the new generation of data science, and advance our mission of promoting the use of data in the understanding of our environment, our social relationships, and our physical and virtual selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops.html</guid>
      <description>All workshops will be online. Participants from all schools are welcome.
 Effective Data Visualization           &amp;nbsp; Sign up    &amp;nbsp; 01/24/22    &amp;nbsp; 5pm - 6:30pm    Visualization is a powerful way to reveal patterns in data, attract attention, and get your message across to an audience quickly and clearly. But, there are many steps in that journey from exploration to information to influence, and many choices to make when putting it all together to tell your story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
